Irving P. Krick papers, 1921-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
Irving P. Krick papers
1921-1996
211
UCLA Library Special Collections
58.0 linear ft. (116 boxes and 3 oversize long boxes)
Collection consists of original meteorological and climatological data (including weather maps and charts) collected by Irving P. Krick and his associates in various states of the U.S., Alberta, Canada, and France.
Krick, Irving
Conditions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 5468716
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ephraim Sales, 2004.
Biography
Irving P. Krick received his B.S. degree in Physics from the University of California, and his M.S. and Ph.D. in meteorology from the California Institute of Technology. He returned to CIT in 1933 to serve as the Chairman for the Department of Meteorology until 1948. Thereafter, Krick oversaw operations as president to a number of his own meteorological companies, including Irving P. Krick Associates Inc. and Irving P. Krick Associates of Canada Ltd. During this time, Krick also served in the U.S. Navy (1942), as well as in the U.S. Army Air Forces, first as the Chief of Long Range Research and Forecasting Section (1942-44), and subsequently as the Deputy Director of Weather Services for the European Theatre of Operations (1944-45). Krick was awarded the U.S. Legion of Merit and Bronze Star with Oak Leaf Cluster, and the Croix de Guerre avec E'toile Vermeil from France.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of original meteorological and climatological data (including weather maps and charts) collected by Irving P. Krick and his associates in various states of the U.S., Alberta, Canada, and France. In addition, there are numerous contracts, correspondence, and weather reports issued to U.S. and foreign clients, including correspondence with and regarding NASA. Correspondence with and information regarding prospective clients is also included, along with personal correspondence, research articles by Krick and his colleagues, newspaper clippings, various court transcripts, generator information, daily summaries, and other miscellany.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged by topic, and includes the following series:
Weather modification operations
Correspondence
Research papers
Paris operations
Strategic Weather Services
Newsletters, books and brochures
U.S. government
Irving P. Krick Associates Inc.
Krick, Irving--Archives.; Meteorologists--United States--Archives.
Container List
- Correspondence
  - Jim Bishop - Alberta, Canada (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Various (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jim Bishop - Alberta, Canada (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Weather Services - Palm Springs, California (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University of Rochester - Rochester, New York (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jack Hubbard - California (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Keith Brandt (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Various - California (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Various - U.S., Canada and Australia (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jim Bishop - Alberta, Canada (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Jim Bishop - Alberta, Canada (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Fred Huenefeld (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Jeanne Collbran, Marie Krick (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Who's Who of America (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Association of Distinguished American Scientists (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Bill Lusk, president of Lusk Companies (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Claudius E. Watts III, president of The Citadel Military College (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Great Eastern Mines inc (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Archdiocese of Los Angeles (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Vladimir A. Miloschevich (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Department of the Navy (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Ferdie Deering (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Ju Ju Lira (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - California Institute of Technology (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Oscar Heinlein (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Lee Cox (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - NASA and regarding (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - NASA and regarding (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - NASA and regarding (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - American Meteorological Society of Northern California (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - White House and President Reagan (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Richard H. Truly, regarding NASA (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - C. Lee Chipman, regarding John E. Wallace and NASA (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - John E. Wallace, of Weather Services Corporation, regarding NASA (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Geof Robillard, regarding shuttle proposal and NASA (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tex McCrary, regarding NASA (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Letter from Robert Khan to the Senators of the U.S. regarding NASA (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Airfleets Incorporated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Morrison Cunningham, Public Works, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Who's Who of America - Certificates (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Regarding plume study (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Regarding plume study (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Regarding Interim Weather Modification Board (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - James Heimbach (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - James Heimbach (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - James Heimbach, Montana State University (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The United States Jaycees (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Foundation Endowment (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - National Law Enforcement Officers Memorial Fund (with certificate of recognition) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Teas National Resource Conservation Commission (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Foundation for the Junior Blind (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Global Life Astrological Profile (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Richard Mendelson, regarding Stags Leap District, Napa, California (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - C. Lee Chipman, regarding C. Itoh data (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Jim Bishop, regarding Snopack proposal (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Ariotex (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ocean Routes Inc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Robert Odom, Louisiana Department of Agriculture (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Texas (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Texas (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Personal (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Personal (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (1 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (2 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - James E. Bednar (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - General (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Prime Minister of Canada, Pierre E. Trudeau (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - C. Lee Chipman (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Richard H. Truly, NASA (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Corporacion Dominicana de Electricidad, Dominican Republic (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Forrest S. McCarthey, NASA (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Harold Haze and Jim Bishop (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Colorado River Board of California (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - C. Lee Chipman (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Jim Bishop, Alberta, Canada (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Roger Mahony, Archibishop of Los Angeles (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Alberta, Canada (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - C. Lee Chipman (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Alberta, Canada (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - J. Hubbard, California (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, with news clippings (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, with articles and papers (1 of 5) (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Misecllaneous, with articles and papers (2 of 5) (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, with articles and papers (3 of 5) (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, with articles and papers (4 of 5) (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, with articles and papers (5 of 5) (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Misecllaneous (2 of 2) (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Paul Caubin to C. Lee Chipman (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - C. Lee Chipman (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Irving P. Krick, Associates Inc.
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Customs Shipments: Canada (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Customs Shipments: Canada (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sales: Canada (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Reports: Canada (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Cloudseeding (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Immigration (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Immigration (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Inter-Company Billing (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Immigration (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Immigration (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations materials (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations materials (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Patent Data (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Conference (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Federal Corporation Income Tax Return (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Report on Weather Modifications for Adams County, Iowa (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Summary of More Important Newspaper Reports Specifically Mentioning Weather as Affecting Military Operations (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Final Report of the Advisory Committee on Weather Control, Vol. 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Expense Report (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Experiment on Wacosin (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Newton C. Stone (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Newton C. Stone (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Employee: Donald Chase (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Employee: Paul J. Caubin (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Various research articles (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Company description (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Operations (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Sales and public relations (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Harald Gunderson, Public Relations Counsel (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Monthly operational reports (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Monthly operational reports (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sales and public relations (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Financial reports (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Generator operator employee data (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Sales and public relations (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Plans and progress (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Generator operator employee data (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Generator operator employee data (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Aircraft bidders, Alberta (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Rainier Development Company, Alberta (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Hall liaison committee, Calgary, Alberta (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Weather Services (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Bond: Oklahoma Weather Modification Act (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Various agreements (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous articles, clippings, mailings, and correspondence (1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous articles, clippings, mailings, and correpsondence (2 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous articles, clippings, mailings, and correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Financial accounts (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Capital Resources Inc. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Television and movie companies (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Television and movie companies (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Staff meetings (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Meeting agenda (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Weather modification articles and newspaper clippings (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Smog proposal (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of Edmonton Seminar (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Prospective clients (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Resume: Robert P. Joseph (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Smog proposal, South Coast, California (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, news articles, and newsletters (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Krick research paper: An Introduction to the Evaluation of Agricultural Cloud Seeding Projects Using Space Age Technology (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Prospects and financial arrangements (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous articles and foreign prospects (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Meterological instrument catalogs (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Aiden Electronic and Impulse Recording Equipment (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings (1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings (2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Inactive generator operators, Louisiana (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Company information (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings (1 of 4) (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings (2 of 4) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correpsondence and clippings (3 of 4) (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings (4 of 4) (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Kirck model generators (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Inactive generator operators, Oklahoma (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Generator operators, Louisiana (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Generator operators, Louisiana (2 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Inactive generator operators, Colorado (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Generator operators, Colorado (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Generator operators, Colorado (2 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles cloud seeding cases: court transcripts, depositions (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Flood Control District vs. Donald R. Campbell, Deposition of J. Robert Stinson (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Southern California Gas Company vs. Gale Drive Associates, Deposition of Pierre Saint- Armand (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Santa Barbara cloud seeding court cases (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Donald R. Campbell vs. Los Angeles County Flood Control District: Ruling on Submitted Motions (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Robert J. Genofile vs. County of Los Angeles: Declaration of Irving P. Krick (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Jenkins Insurance Agency (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Interview with Irving P. Krick (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Copies of work orders and invoices (1 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Copies of work orders and invoices (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Donald R. Campbell vs. Los Angeles County Flood Control (1 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Donald R. Campbell vs. Los Angeles County Flood Control (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Jerome Ott vs. State of California (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Qualley firm case (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Various court cases (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Various court cases (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Rita Acosta vs. County of Los Angeles (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Donald R. Campebell vs. Los Angeles County Flood Control (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Michigan lawsuit (1 of 2) (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Michigan lawsuit (2 of 2) (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - IPK Company information (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - VIA Computers (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Covenant of Non-competition (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - American Institute of Aerological Research: Bureau vouchers (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Generator operators timesheets (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Tax forms and documents (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Olin, Energy Systems Division (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and articles (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (1 of 3) (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (2 of 3) (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (3 of 3) (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (1 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (2 of 2) (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Weather Services, brochures (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (1 of 2) (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Teel Irrigation, Eagle Ranch, Oregon (2 of 2) (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Krick (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum vitae, articles about and by Krick (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Suggested Readings for Strategic Weather Services Meteorologists on the Job Training (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - The Krick Methodology of Weather Forecasts for Years into the Future (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Paper: The Role of Local Governmental Units in Weather Modification: California, by Sho Sato (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Weather Investment Opportujnities Through Application of the Expertise of the Krick Group (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Various memos (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Client endorsements (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, articles and news clippings (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Disney Co., Educational television program (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - American Meteorological Society (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Evolution of the Krick Group (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Article regarding Krick in Pilot Light, Vol. 39, No. 2 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Articles regarding NASA Challenger (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Memos: Staff meetings (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit, news clippings (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit, correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit, correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Michael Reinbold vs. Krick, Michigan: Proceedings (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Michael Reinbold vs. Krick, Michigan: Deposition of Bernard H. DeWitt (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Michael Reinbold vs. Krick, Michigan: Deposition of Michael Reinbold (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Paper: Cloud Seeding in Michigan, by D.E. Linvill (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - News clippings: Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - News clippings: Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - California court cases: Deposition of Arnold Court (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Article: Expert Witnesses in Weather Modification Legal Proceedings, by Ray Jay Davis and Pierre St.-Amand (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Paper: Flash Flood Events, by R.A. Maddox et al. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Deloitte, Haskins and Sells (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Agro-tech, Hawaii (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Court case: F.W. Phillips vs. City of Lawton, Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Court case: F.W. Phillips vs. City of Lawton, Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - TRW Inc., California (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Michigan lawsuit, news clippings (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Michigan lawsuit, legal papers (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit (1 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit (2 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Various court cases (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Carl Byoir and Associates, Inc. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - The Associates of the California Institute of Technology (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Why and How the Krick System of Cloud Seeding Works (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - State Employment reports: Nebraska (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Property of Water Resources Development Corp. sticker (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Evolution fo the D-Day Weather Forecast: An Interview of Dr. Iriving Krick (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Newsletters and Brochures
  - Tenneco Inc. Annual Report (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Boyd Quake's Predictions (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Bulletin, No. 13 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - The Zone, Vol. 1, No. 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Newsletters, Books and Brochures
  - Bulletin of the American Meteorological Society, Vol. 66, No. 4 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Drexel Burnham Lambert, Annual Report (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - AT&T Annual Report (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Packaged Food Industry Update (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Workbook of Atmospheric Dispertion Estimates: D. Bruce Turner (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - California Institute of Technology Report (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - California Institute of Technology Engineering and Science, Vol. LVI, No. 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - EOS: Vol. 67, No. 42, pp. 793-808 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Brochure: Technifex Inc. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin of the American Meteorological Society, Vol. 66, No. 5-6 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - National Geographic Research, Vol. 1, No. 3 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Human Dimensions of Weather Modification, by W.R. Derrick Sewell (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Northern Wheatbelt Cloud Study (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Business Week, Special bonus issue: The Corporate Elite, Top 1000 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - University of California 1982 Honor Roll (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Pineena: A Profile of the Water Resources Commission (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Westways, Vol. 67, No. 6 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - The Teke, Vol. 76, No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - The Teke Hall of Fame (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - True, Vol. 43, No. 297 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - C. Itoh and Co., brochures and annual report (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Washington Economics Inc. Forecast (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - California Institute of Technology, Engineering and Science, Vol. LI, No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Meteorological Instruments Catalog (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Aviation History (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Storm-Central Phase, Preliminary Program Design (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Playing to Win: The Small Business Guide to Survival and Growth, by Stephen M. Pollan and Mark Levine (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - California Institute of Technology, Engineering and Science, Vol. XLVII, No. 2 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Potential for Weather Modification in Alberta, A Five Year Study, 1980-85 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - U.S. News and World Report, Vol. 105, No. 23 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Systems: Vol. XXI, No. 2 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Gifts for Environmental Action (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - 1982 Associates of the California Institute of Technology (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - The Explorers Club: Roster and Handbook (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Grainger's Motor Book, No. 299 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - California Institute of Technology, Alumni Directory (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - National Office Management Association: Manual of Practical Office Short Cuts (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Paris Operations
  - General data and correspondence (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous bills (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Employees (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - European data (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Client relations (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Agencies (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Project organization (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Locations: Baux (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Prospects (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - European planning (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Agencies (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Personal data (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Bourg St. Maruice (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Alger (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous contracts (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - SODETEP and Alger, finances (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Roger Tuffery (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - SODETEP: Employment (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Faugere & Jutheau (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Training (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Work permits (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Tunisia, client relations (Box 97, Folder 4)